<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>SF Civic Tech Blog</title><description>News from SF Civic Tech</description><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org</link><item><title>SF Open Referral</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2014-07-26-sf-open-referral</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2014-07-26-sf-open-referral</guid><description>Agencies and organizations create and maintain many different community resource directories. Each organization applies similar resources and effort against a shared issue, but there is no shared knowledge. Although they share similar goals and challenges, these efforts work in isolation of each other. SF Open Referral improves social service delivery through shared, open resource data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2014 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>LocalFreeWeb</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2014-09-05-localfreeweb</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2014-09-05-localfreeweb</guid><description>Many organizations and institutions offer access to free, internet-enabled computers, but there is no way for someone to find these locations without being online already. In short, you need the internet to find the internet. LocalFreeWeb makes it so all you need is a cell phone.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How our Campaign Data Visualization App Can Help YOU This Election</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2014-10-22-how-our-campaign-data-visualization-app-can-help-y</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2014-10-22-how-our-campaign-data-visualization-app-can-help-y</guid><description>On November 4th, San Franciscans head to the polls to vote for, amongst other things, a tax on carbonated beverages (aka “Soda”). Did you know that pro-soda tax individuals and committees have raised $224,971 to pass the ordinance, while the soda industry has raised $7,700,000 to defeat it? Check out our visualizations of campaign financing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Speaker: Matt Arana on Accessibility</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2014-10-22-speaker-matt-arana-on-accessibility</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2014-10-22-speaker-matt-arana-on-accessibility</guid><description>The SF Brigade was fortunate to get an introduction to accessibility from Matt Arana from SSB BART Group, which has been helping organizations be more accessible since 1997. Matt’s introduction to accessibility came when he was working for a tobacco company. He had an opportunity to work for SSB BART instead, but wasn’t sure if it was a good career move. Since family and faith are important to Matt, he discussed it with his aunt before they went to services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SF Brigade Hosts CityCampSF</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2015-01-07-sf-brigade-hosts-citycampsf</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2015-01-07-sf-brigade-hosts-citycampsf</guid><description>What happens when you gather local officials, city staff, entrepreneurs, designers, developers, journalists and citizens in a room for one day, and ask for their best ideas to improve their communities? You get CityCamp - a lot of excitement, a little chaos, plenty of solutions, and a whole lot of action.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Announcing C4SF sponsor: Microsoft</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2015-01-18-announcing-c4sf-sponsor-microsoft</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2015-01-18-announcing-c4sf-sponsor-microsoft</guid><description>As Captain of Code for San Francisco, it is my pleasure to announce &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.microsoftbayarea.com/&quot;&gt;Microsoft&lt;/a&gt; as the Brigade&amp;#39;s first sponsor.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2015 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Celebrating the Life of Our Friend, Ethan Lang</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2015-04-09-celebrating-the-life-of-our-friend-ethan-lang</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2015-04-09-celebrating-the-life-of-our-friend-ethan-lang</guid><description>Ethan loved to bring people together through music. His friends, family and loved ones will never forget his footloose spirit and ability to always get them on a dance floor. In Turkey, he was known to dance at a traditional turkish bar with locals in a bar mitzvah-type circle. In 2011, while celebrating at the Boston Marathon, he never stopped jiving to the street music, despite warning from policemen. &amp;quot;Dancin&amp;#39; ain&amp;#39;t illegal,&amp;quot; he&amp;#39;d say. He inspired people around him to enjoy life to the fullest and not take anything too seriously. His dance moves could cure anyone during the saddest of times – and they still do.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>April 12, 2015: Campaign Finance Summit</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2015-04-29-april-12-2015-campaign-finance-summit</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2015-04-29-april-12-2015-campaign-finance-summit</guid><description>Our Campaign Finance Summit featured a speaker series followed by a visual data exploration hackathon. Below we have outlined the motivating issues for Open Campaign Finance Data along with updates on resources that can further keep us informed. The issues are followed up by a summary and video of each speaker&amp;#39;s contribution to the discussion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Text if you’re happy or not says tech volunteer group</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2015-06-01-text-if-youre-happy-or-not-says-tech-volunteer-gro</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2015-06-01-text-if-youre-happy-or-not-says-tech-volunteer-gro</guid><description>Code for San Francisco volunteer hackers launched the Happiness Survey to better understand the Bay Area state of mind.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CodeAcross SF 2016</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2016-03-24-codeacross-sf-2016</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2016-03-24-codeacross-sf-2016</guid><description>On March 5 we organized the third annual CodeAcross in San Francisco. The event, which was hosted at Microsoft Reactor, was part of a nationwide effort around the world to bring together people who want to collaborate to make their cities better. And collaborate we did! Nearly 100 people joined us to work on projects that benefit the community and San Francisco.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2016 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet SF Brigade Members</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2016-04-09-meet-sf-brigade-members</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2016-04-09-meet-sf-brigade-members</guid><description>We’re kicking off our #MeetSFBrigadeMembers series with April Steed – a UX designer, passionate civic hacker, and Project Lead for Lighten. Read on to find out how she got involved with Code for SF, what drives her and how Lighten is making access to social services more user friendly!</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SF Brigade&apos;s Data Science Working Group</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2016-04-26-sf-brigades-data-science-working-group</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2016-04-26-sf-brigades-data-science-working-group</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The past couple of months have been an exciting time for the Data Science
Group Working Group (DWSG). The group, which started in January, brings together
both professional data scientists and data enthusiasts hoping to improve their skills
whilst making an impact. DSWG uses the wealth of open source data made available
by SF Open Data and others to work on both its own projects as well as to support
other civic hackers at Code for San Francisco. By providing data science expertise
they’ve become a central resource to the broader SF Brigade.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>VR Data Visualization: A New Way to Address Community Issues</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2016-08-15-vr-data-visualization-a-new-way-to-address-communi</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2016-08-15-vr-data-visualization-a-new-way-to-address-communi</guid><description>A San Francisco Brigade team has been partnering with SFHIP for almost a year now on a data visualization project that looks at alcohol licenses in San Francisco, specifically those establishments that sell alcohol to be sold off premise. Before any mapping or visualization could happened, SFHIP reached out to community advocates to find out first hand how the easy access to alcohol was impacting their communities. SFHIP lead community focus discussions in three SF neighborhoods, Bayview, Tenderloin and the Mission. SF Brigade members participated in these community listening sessions and helped SFHIP distill the findings using user centered design principles.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Announcing C4SF sponsor: Segment</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2016-11-17-announcing-c4sf-sponsor-segment</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2016-11-17-announcing-c4sf-sponsor-segment</guid><description>Code for San Francisco is happy to announce that Segment has contributed $5,047 to support our efforts. A huge, sincere thank you to Segment!</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Community Forum - Week 1</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2016-11-23-community-forum-week-1</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2016-11-23-community-forum-week-1</guid><description>We at Code for San Francisco have one goal: to positively impact our community by means of the skills at our disposal, which for many of us means leveraging various technologies to meet a community need. This goal can be often distilled into two words: &lt;em&gt;civic tech&lt;/em&gt;. And here in the Bay Area we have at our disposal a seemingly endless supply of technologists: developers, designers, data scientists, product managers, and many many more. I think in our city, as a collective community dedicated to civic tech, we do not have a lack of engagement on the latter half of that phrase. The former half, however, the &lt;em&gt;civic&lt;/em&gt; in &lt;em&gt;civic tech&lt;/em&gt;, is the real tricky part to get right. If the past election has taught us nothing, it has taught us that civic engagement with our communities is not something that can be underestimated nor ignored.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Project Investment Fund Launches</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2017-02-09-project-investment-fund-launches</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2017-02-09-project-investment-fund-launches</guid><description>Code for San Francisco is happy to announce we are launching a new partnership with Microsoft to support the work of our volunteers. Beginning today, projects organized through Code for San Francisco can apply to access up to $2,000 to spend on anything they need to build stronger solutions; e.g. web hosting, training, data processing, user testing, or more! We are excited to begin this new experiment and look forward to seeing where it leads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2016 SF Brigade Year in Review</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2017-02-16-2016-sf-brigade-year-in-review</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2017-02-16-2016-sf-brigade-year-in-review</guid><description>2016 was defined by broken politics. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.americandialect.org/dumpster-fire-is-2016-american-dialect-society-word-of-the-year&quot;&gt;Dumpster fire&lt;/a&gt; was chosen as “best representing the public discourse and preoccupations of the past year.” While the world of politics looks completely dysfunctional, Code for San Francisco folks continue to meet in growing numbers, committed to the ideal that our politics and government can work better for people by leveraging technology.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Searching for Equity in a Sea of Data</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2017-03-17-searching-for-equity-in-a-sea-of-data</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2017-03-17-searching-for-equity-in-a-sea-of-data</guid><description>Open Data Day is an annual celebration of open data all over the world. This year, it was celebrated on Saturday, March 4. Code for San Francisco hosted its Open Data Day event at the &lt;a href=&quot;http://microsoftreactor.com/venue/sf-reactor/&quot;&gt;Microsoft Reactor&lt;/a&gt; and launched the day with an inspiring keynote by Carla Mays. &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/CarlaMays&quot;&gt;@CarlaMays&lt;/a&gt; is a veteran of the Civic tech movement and this was a bit of a homecoming for her having attended Open Data Day’s previous incarnation, Code Across in 2013. Carla discussed how open data could be used to create a more equitable and inclusive society. &amp;quot;We&amp;#39;ve really got to start to see the faces of this change, it&amp;#39;s got to be more inclusive and we&amp;#39;ve got to work as a team.&amp;quot; She also stressed that “We have to address biases that are baked into data sets.” The key to inclusiveness and equity is what Carla tagged</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spring 2017 Project Demo Night</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2017-05-28-spring-2017-project-demo-night</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2017-05-28-spring-2017-project-demo-night</guid><description>There’s nothing like a Demo Night to help a team focus their presentation and take stock of where they are in their project. It is also a great opportunity to recruit for their project and show the rest of the Brigade the work they’ve been up to. Eleven teams presented their projects and the progress the teams are making is inspiring. The project teams are working on a wide range of issues facing San Francisco residents from helping the homeless to analyzing juvenile justice sentencing disparities. Check out the videos from the teams presentations and join us every Wednesday night hacking for San Francisco!</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Noob: A First Timer&apos;s Account of Code for San Francisco Civic Hack Night</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2017-07-31-noob-a-first-timers-account-of-code-for-san-franci</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2017-07-31-noob-a-first-timers-account-of-code-for-san-franci</guid><description>My very first &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.codeforamerica.org/blog/2013/07/24/brigade-101-how-to-hack-night/&quot;&gt;Code for America Civic Hack Night&lt;/a&gt; began with pressing a buzzer to gain entry to the Code for America building in San Francisco&amp;#39;s SoMa district. A very welcoming receptionist greeted me and noticed right away that I was new. He pointed me towards the red name tags for newbies (as opposed to the blue name tags for returning attendees). The color coding of newbies and repeat attendees, plus the use of name tags in the first place, made it so much easier to strike up conversations with people and quickly learn why each attendee decided to spend their Wednesday night volunteering.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Day of Civic Hacking 2017: How We Learned to Deal with Disasters</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2017-10-17-national-day-of-civic-hacking-2017-how-we-learned-</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2017-10-17-national-day-of-civic-hacking-2017-how-we-learned-</guid><description>Live long enough in California and you might experience an earthquake, wildfire, catastrophic flood from winter rains, extreme drought, and those are just the natural events. C4SF decided to do something a little different this year for NDoCH. Rather than a two or three day event, we decided to do a one-day deeper exploration of resilience and disaster preparedness in our neighborhoods.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Designers &amp; Geeks Provoke SF Crime Data</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2017-11-25-designers-geeks-provoke-sf-crime-data</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2017-11-25-designers-geeks-provoke-sf-crime-data</guid><description>Code for San Francisco first collaboration with Designers &amp;amp; Geeks leads off Provoke, a new event series.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Code for America Brigade Congress</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-01-21-code-for-america-brigade-congress</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-01-21-code-for-america-brigade-congress</guid><description>The report back from Code for San Franicisco&amp;#39;s Brigade contingent to the 2017 Code for America Brigade Congress.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Code for San Francisco Site Relaunch</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-02-05-site-relaunch</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-02-05-site-relaunch</guid><description>The return to Jekyll</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Code for San Francisco Project Investment Fund Relaunch</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-03-07-project-investment-fund</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-03-07-project-investment-fund</guid><description>Project investment fund releaunch</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Open Data Day 2018 Recap</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-04-11-open-data-day-recap</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-04-11-open-data-day-recap</guid><description>Open Data Day 2018 Recap</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In Loving Memory of Sanat</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-04-27-in-loving-memory-of-sanat</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-04-27-in-loving-memory-of-sanat</guid><description>A tribute to our dear friend Sanat Moningi, we miss you.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small Business Administration Case Study</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-04-30-sba-case-study</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-04-30-sba-case-study</guid><description>A look at how Code for San Francisco&amp;#39;s Data Science Working group was able to work with the local Small Business Administration office to develop a tool to analyze loan data and answer questions to increase the office&amp;#39;s impact.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Mapping Tools for Brigades</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-06-14-mapping-tools</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-06-14-mapping-tools</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The Civic Innovation Group has built a suite of tools that Brigade members can use to remove roadblacks and
save time when working with filtering and mapping data, especially for people who don&amp;#39;t have map coding skills.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Open Data Science Conference West 2018</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-08-04-odsc</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-08-04-odsc</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Partnership post from Open Data Science Conference West 2018
upcoming Oct. 31 - Nov. 3.  ODSC West will be this Fall&amp;#39;s leading
data science conference providing over 340 hours of trainings,
talks, and workshops spanning 4 days and 48 tracks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>dev/Mission and C4SF Launch Fellowship Program at National Day of Civic Hacking</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-09-16-dev-mission-and-c4sf-launch-fellowship-program-at-national-day-of-civic-hacking</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-09-16-dev-mission-and-c4sf-launch-fellowship-program-at-national-day-of-civic-hacking</guid><description>Leo Sosa of dev/Mission gave the keynote at C4SF&amp;#39;s National Day of Civic Hacking event. In the following interview he describes his vision for bringing equity to tech employment and how C4SF can help.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Code for San Francisco Community Creates a Voter Guide to Help Fight Fake News.</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-10-20-code-for-san-francisco-community-creates-a-voter-guide-to-help-fight-fake-news</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2018-10-20-code-for-san-francisco-community-creates-a-voter-guide-to-help-fight-fake-news</guid><description>We Vote is nonpartisan and nonprofit, founded and built by volunteers, including engineers from the Code for San Francisco Brigade of Code for America. We Vote is a networked digital voter guide that empowers voters and improves democracy. </description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>W.O.M.A.N., Inc. Domestic Violence Referral Center</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2019-04-17-w-o-m-a-n-inc-domestic-violence-referral-center</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2019-04-17-w-o-m-a-n-inc-domestic-violence-referral-center</guid><description>This February, W.O.M.A.N., Inc. and Code for San Francisco volunteers launched a revamped version of DVIRC, a database that helps domestic violence agencies connect information with the survivors who need it. Shaena Spoor, the project representative from W.O.M.A.N., Inc., tells the story of how it came together. </description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Open Data Day 2019 - Community Driven Hackathon</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2019-05-01-open-data-day-2019-community-driven-hackathon</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2019-05-01-open-data-day-2019-community-driven-hackathon</guid><description>An open source report from your local civic tech community.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Introducing Civic Tech to San Francisco&apos;s Underserved Communities</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2019-06-22-introducing-civc-tech-to-san-franciscos-underserved-communities</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2019-06-22-introducing-civc-tech-to-san-franciscos-underserved-communities</guid><description>Code for San Francisco teams up with &amp;lt;dev/Mission&amp;gt; to create a Fellowship program to introduce San Francisco&amp;#39;s underserved youth to civic tech.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Code for San Francisco 2019 Year in Review</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2020-02-06-code-for-san-francisco-2019-year-in-review</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2020-02-06-code-for-san-francisco-2019-year-in-review</guid><description>2019 was a very busy year for the Code for SF community!</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet Niko: From the Classroom to UX</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2021-04-07-from-classroom-to-ux</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2021-04-07-from-classroom-to-ux</guid><description>Moving from education to user experience</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dev/Mission, Uber, C4SF Fellowship</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2021-07-13-dev-mission-uber-c4sf-fellowship</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2021-07-13-dev-mission-uber-c4sf-fellowship</guid><description>Civic Tech Design 101 for the Next Generation of Tech Talent</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crafting Impactful Narratives with Technologists for the Public Good</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2024-05-15-crafting-impactful-narratives</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2024-05-15-crafting-impactful-narratives</guid><description>SF Civic Tech and Technologists for the Public Good hosted their first in-person event post-Covid. The gathering featured insights from civic tech veterans Tom Dooner, Marnie Webb, and Nick Okafor, who shared expertise on effective storytelling, stakeholder engagement, and integrating STEM education with social equity to drive meaningful change in public interest technology.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>(Re-)Introducing SF Civic Tech</title><link>http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2024-10-16-re-introducing-sf-civic-tech</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sfcivictech.org/blog/2024-10-16-re-introducing-sf-civic-tech</guid><description>SF Civic Tech was founded in 2013 as Code for San Francisco as part of the Code for America Brigade Network. At the beginning of 2023, Code for America announced that it would “sunset” the Brigade Network so by the end of that same year, Code for San Francisco renamed itself to SF Civic Tech. In 2024 SF Civic Tech incorporated as a 501(c)3 tax-exempt non-profit.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>